{
  "name": "",
  "isFavorite": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Car",
      "back": "Araba"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Bus",
      "back": "Otobüs"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Train",
      "back": "Tren"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Plane",
      "back": "Uçak"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Ship",
      "back": "Gemi"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Boat",
      "back": "Tekne"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Taxi",
      "back": "Taksi"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Bicycle",
      "back": "Bisiklet"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Motorcycle",
      "back": "Motosiklet"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Truck",
      "back": "Kamyon"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Van",
      "back": "Minibüs"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Subway",
      "back": "Metro"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Helicopter",
      "back": "Helikopter"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Tram",
      "back": "Tramvay"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Scooter",
      "back": "Scooter"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Skateboard",
      "back": "Kaykay"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Rollerblades",
      "back": "Paten"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Canoe",
      "back": "Kano"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Yacht",
      "back": "Yat"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Hot air balloon",
      "back": "Sıcak hava balonu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Spaceship",
      "back": "Uzay gemisi"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Ambulance",
      "back": "Ambulans"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Police car",
      "back": "Polis arabası"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Fire truck",
      "back": "İtfaiye aracı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cable car",
      "back": "Teleferik"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Jet",
      "back": "Jet"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Hovercraft",
      "back": "Hovercraft"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Rickshaw",
      "back": "Tuk tuk"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Sled",
      "back": "Kızak"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cart",
      "back": "Araba (el arabası vs.)"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Trailer",
      "back": "Römork"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Caravan",
      "back": "Karavan"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Monorail",
      "back": "Tek raylı tren"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cruise ship",
      "back": "Yolcu gemisi"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Ferry",
      "back": "Feribot"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Jet ski",
      "back": "Jet ski"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Segway",
      "back": "Segway"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Bulldozer",
      "back": "Dozer"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Forklift",
      "back": "Forklift"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Tractor",
      "back": "Traktör"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Wheelchair",
      "back": "Tekerlekli sandalye"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Stroller",
      "back": "Bebek arabası"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Horse carriage",
      "back": "At arabası"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Submarine",
      "back": "Denizaltı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Tanker",
      "back": "Tanker"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Rowboat",
      "back": "Kürekli sandal"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Electric scooter",
      "back": "Elektrikli scooter"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Minivan",
      "back": "Aile arabası"
    }
  ]
}
